<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Knotty</string>
    <string name="knot_name_1">Improved Clinch Knot</string>
    <string name="knot_name_2">Snell Knot</string>
    <string name="knot_name_3">Palomar Knot</string>
    <string name="knot_name_4">Turle Knot</string>
    <string name="knot_name_5">Uni Knot</string>
    <string name="knot_name_6">Trilene Knot</string>
    <string name="knot_name_7">Rapala Knot</string>
    <string name="knot_name_8">San Diego Jam Knot</string>
    <string name="knot_name_9">Arbour Knot</string>
    <string name="knot_name_10">Blood Knot</string>
    <string name="knot_name_11">Yucatan Knot</string>
    <string name="knot_name_12">Surgeon\'s Knot</string>
    <string name="knot_name_13">Double Uni Knot</string>
    <string name="knot_name_14">Nail Knot</string>
    <string name="knot_name_15">Albright Knot</string>
    <string name="knot_name_16">Dropper Loop</string>
    <string name="knot_name_17">Surgeon\'s Loop</string>
    <string name="knot_name_18">Perfection Loop</string>
    <string name="knot_name_19">Spider Hitch</string>
    <string name="knot_name_20">Bimini Twist</string>
    <string name="knot_description_1">Used to secure lures, hooks and swivels to the fishing line. Only pull the long end to tighten.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_2">Used to attach a tippet or leader directly to a baited hook. Mainly for eyeless hooks.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_3">Used to secure hooks and swivels to the fishing line. One of the strongest knots.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_4">Used to connect a fly or hook to a leader, makes line emerge perpendicular to the hook shaft.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_5">Used to connect the line to the hook but also connects the line to the arbour of a reel or swivel.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_6">Used to tie lines to hooks, snaps, lures and swivels. Retains around 90 percent of the line’s original strength.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_7">Used for tying directly to the lure. (e.g. no swivel). It retains most of the line strength.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_8">Used to attach line to a swivel, hook, artificial fly or clip. Very popular knot.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_9">Used to secure the line to the spool of the fishing reel. Helps anchor backing to the reel arbour for bigger fish.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_10">Used to join two parts of fishing line with similar thickness.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_11">Used to connect a doubled main line to a heavy leader. Strong knot for mono-filament leader to braided line.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_12">Used to join together two piece of fishing line of varying thickness.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_13">Used to join lines of either varying or similar strengths.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_14">Used to connect the fly line to the leader. Good for lines with different diameters.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_15">Used to join two fishing lines of different materials and diameters together.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_16">Used to form a secure structure for making multiple hook bait rings.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_17">Used to create a quick end loop in leaders and lines to connect them to other loops. It is easy and retains strength.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_18">Used for building leaders that can be clipped into a swivel, easy knot for fly-fishing.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_19">Used to form a double line or a loop in the line for light tackle fishing it is easy to tie and retains most of the line’s strength.</string>
    <string name="knot_description_20">Used to make a double line leader and for loop-to-loop connections. Retains almost all strength.</string>
    <string name="expand_more_content_description">Click to see how tie knot step by step</string>
</resources>